<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.video.udemy" name="Udemy" provider-name="SlyGuy" version="0.9.1">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.slyguy"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py" provides="video">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en">Online Courses - Learn Anything, On Your Schedule</description>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news>Support latest Widevine sources</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.alivegr.artwork" name="AliveGR Artwork" version="3.0.5" provider-name="Twilight0">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false" type="AliveGR" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">AliveGR's main artwork</summary>
		<description lang="en">Artwork is distributed separately to allow easier maintenance and consume less bandwidth</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.AliveGR" name="AliveGR" version="2.9.1" provider-name="Twilight0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="18.0.000"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.artwork" version="3.0.5"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.logos" version="1.0.2"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.28"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl.pluginsgr" version="0.0.13"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="2.9.10"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.8.10"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pyxbmct" version="1.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video audio image executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/modules/service.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">AliveGR addon for Kodi media center</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">AliveGR is an addon allowing streaming content available mostly in Greek language.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">AliveGR's author does not host, stream or distribute any of the content displayed inside this software and cannot be held responsible for the quality or availability of the listed streams.
On demand content is scraped from various websites and is freely available on the internet on public domains. This software acts only as a search engine.
Kindly note that AliveGR is not an official part of the media player you are running, and therefore not to be mentioned within official support channels, this addon has nothing to do with the media player itself, nor it’s intended use, it is simply a third party plugin which has been added to your system and it is provided "as is" with no warranty.</disclaimer>
        <summary lang="el_GR">AliveGR, Μικροεφαρμογή για το κέντρο πολυμέσων Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το πρόσθετο AliveGR επιτρέπει την θέαση ροών με περιεχόμενο κυρίως εις την Ελληνική γλώσσα.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Ο δημιουργός του AliveGR δεν φιλοξενεί ή παρέχει οποιοδήποτε από τα απεικονιζόμενα πολυμέσα και περιεχόμένο εντός του μενού του και δεν μπορεί να θεωρηθεί υπεύθυνος για την ποιότητα ή την διαθεσιμότητα των ροών.
Το περιεχόμενο αναπαραγωγής κατά βούληση φιλτράρεται από διάφορες ιστοσελίδες ελεύθερα διαθέσιμες στο διαδίκτυο σε δημόσιους ιστότοπους. Το παρόν λογισμικό ενεργεί μόνο ως μηχανή αναζήτησης.
Παρακαλώ προσέξτε ότι το AliveGR δεν είναι επίσημο κομμάτι του αναπαραγωγέα πολυμέσων Kodi ή της καθορισμένης χρήσης του, είναι απλά μία μικροεφαρμογή που προστέθηκε στο σύστημά σας και που παρέχεται "όπως είναι" χωρίς καμία εγγύηση καλής λειτουργίας.</disclaimer>
        <language>en el</language>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <forum>https://github.com/Twilight0/plugin.video.AliveGR/issues</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/Twilight0/plugin.video.AliveGR</source>
        <website>https://alivegr.net/</website>
        <size>1500240</size>
        <news>+ [COLOR green]2.9.X[/COLOR] [I]27-04-2021 - 03-05-2021[/I]
- Some bug fixes
- Check streams when picking a stream sequentially (default being off)
- Removed playlist mode from vod stream choices

+ [COLOR red]2.8.X[/COLOR] [I]25-03-2021 - 20-04-2021[/I]
- Change caching method
- New settings.xml for Matrix+
- Labeling tweaks for directory mode
- Debugging mode tweaks
- Removed cache delete functions
- Pagination is now disabled by default
- Remove Euronews items
- Bumped dependencies
- Some bug fixes
- Various other insignificant tweaks</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/media/main_menu.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/live_streams.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/movies.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/tv_series.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/networks.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.opensubtitles"
       name="OpenSubtitles.org"
       version="5.2.15"
       provider-name="amet, opensubtitles, juokelis">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module"
             library="service.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">OpenSubtitles</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Search and download subtitles for movies and TV-Series from OpenSubtitles.org. Search in 75 languages, 4.000.000+ subtitles, daily updates.</description>
		<description lang="ast_ES">Pelis and Subtítulos TV en munches llingües, milenta de subtítulos traducíos y xubíos caldía. Descarga llibre dende la fonte, sofitu API, millones d'usuarios.</description>
		<description lang="br_FR">Istitloù Filmoù ha TV e meur a yezh, miliadoù a istitloù troet hag uskarget bemdez. Pellgargadenn digoust diouzh ar vammenn, skoazell an API, millionoù a implijerien.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Subtítols de films i televisió en múltiples idiomes, milers de subtítols traduïts carregats diàriament. Descàrrega gratuïta des de la font, suport de l'API, amb milions d'usuaris.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Titulky k filmům a seriálům v mnoha jazycích, denně tisíce nahraných přeložených titulků. Stažení zadarmo přímo od zdroje, podpora API, milióny uživatelů.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Film- und TV-Untertitel in vielen Sprachen, täglicher Upload von tausenden übersetzten Untertiteln. Freier Download von der Quelle, API-Unterstützung, Millionen Nutzer</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Ταινίες και Σειρές σε όλες τις γλώσσες, χιλιάδες μεταφρασμένοι υπότιτλοι ανεβαίνουν καθημερινά, κατεβάστε δωρεάν , υποστήριξη API από εκατομμύρια χρήστες</description>
		<description lang="eo_EO">Filmaj kaj Televidaj subtekstoj en multaj lingvoj, miloj da tradukitaj subtekstoj ĉiutage alŝutataj. Senpaga elŝuto de fonto, API-subteno, miloj da uzantoj.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Películas y Subtítulos en diversos idiomas, miles de subtítulos traducidos subidos diariamente. Descarge gratis, soporte API, millones de usuarios.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Sadu Filmi ja TV Serjaalide subtiitrid erinevates keeltes laetakse üles igapäev. tasuta allalaadimine ja abi, rohkem kui miljon kasutajat.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Film eta Telebista azpitituluak hizkuntza anitzetan, milaka azpititulu itzuliak igotzen dira egunero. Doan jaitsi iturburutik, API sostengua, milioika erabiltzaile.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Tekstityksiä useilla kielillä elokuviin ja TV-Sarjoihin, tuhansia uusia tekstityksiä päivittäin, ilmainen lataus, API tuki, miljoonia käyttäjiä.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Les sous-titres de film et téléfilm en plusieurs langues, des milliers de sous-titres traduits tous les jours. Bénéficiez de téléchargements gratuits depuis la source, du support API, une d'une communauté de millions d'utilisateurs.</description>
		<description lang="hi_IN">मूवी और टीवी उपशीर्षक कई भाषाओं में अनुवाद उपशीर्षक के हजारों दैनिक अपलोड की गई। मुफ्त डाउनलोड स्रोत से , एपीआई समर्थन, उपयोगकर्ताओं के लाखों लोगों की ।</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, tisuće prijevoda postavljenih svaki dan. Besplatno preuzimanje s izvora, podrška za API, milijuni korisnika.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Film és TV feliratok több nyelven, naponta több ezer lefordított felirat feltöltés. Ingyenes letöltés a forrástól, API támogatás, több millió felhasználó.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Subjudul film dan serial TV dalam multibahasa, ribuan subjudul diterjemah dan diunggah setiap harinya. Pengunduhan gratis dari sumber, didukung fitur antarmuka pemrograman aplikasi, dan jutaan pengguna.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Textar fyrir myndir og sjónvarpsþ. á mörgum tungumálum, þúsundir af þýddum textum upphlaðið daglega. Frítt niðurhal frá síðu, API stuðningur, milljónir notenda.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Sottotitoli di Film e TV in più lingue,migliaia di sottotitoli tradotti caricati ogni giorno.Download gratuito,supporto API, milioni di utenti.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">映画やテレビの字幕をさまざまな言語で。毎日数多くの翻訳字幕がアップロードされています。ソースを無料ダウンロード、API 対応、数百万を超えるユーザー。</description>
		<description lang="ka_GR">სუბტიტრები ფილმებისა და ტვ-სთვის მრავალ ენაზე. ათასობიტ თარგმნილი სუბტიტრის ატვირთვა ყოველდღიურად. უდასო ჩამოტვირტვა წყაროდან, API მხარდაჭერა, მილიონობით მომხმარებელი</description>
		<description lang="km_KH">អត្ថបទរឿងសម្រាប់ ខ្សែភាពយន្ត និងកម្មវិធីទូរទស្សន៍​ ជាភាសាជាច្រើន រួមនឹងអត្ថបទរឿងបកប្រែរាប់ពាន់​រឿង​ដែល​ត្រូវបាន​អ័ពឡូដជារៀងរាល់ថ្ងៃ។ ទាញយកដោយឥតគិតថ្លៃពីប្រភពដើម គាំទ្រ API និងមានអ្នកប្រើប្រាស់រាប់លាននាក់។ </description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Movie and TV Subtitles in multiple languages, thousands of translated subtitles uploaded daily. Free download from source, API support, millions of users.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Sarikata TV dan Movie dalam pelbagai bahasa, ribuan terjemahan sarikata dimuat-naik setiap hari.Muat-turun percuma dari sumber utama, sokongan API, jutaan pengguna.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Ondertitels voor films en tv-series in meerdere talen, dagelijks upload van duizenden vertaalde ondertitels. Gratis downloaden van de bron, API ondersteuning, miljoenen gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="no_NO">Undertekster for film og TV på mange språk, med tusener av nye oversettelser hver dag. Vi har gratis nedlasting av undertekster, API-support, og mange millioner brukere.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Napisy do filmów i seriali w wielu językach. Tysiące napisów dodawanych codziennie. Darmowe pobranie, miliony użytkowników.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Milhares de legendas para filmes e seriados de TV, em vários idiomas, são traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download grátis, suporte API e milhões de usuários.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">Legendas de filmes e séries de TV em vários idiomas, milhares de legendas traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download grátis a partir da fonte, suporte API, milhões de utilizadores.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Subtitrari pentru filme in multe limbi, mii de subtitrari traduse si încărcate in fiecare zi. Descărca gratuit de la sursă, suport API, milioane de utilizatori.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Кино и ТВ субтитры на нескольких языках, тысячи переведенными субтитрами загружены ежедневно. Бесплатно скачать из исходных текстов, поддержка API, миллионы пользователей.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Titulky pre filmy a TV seriály, denne nahratých tisíce titulkov preložených vo viacerých jazykoch. Sťahuj zadarmo zo zdroja, podpora API, milióny používateľov.</description>
		<description lang="sl_SI">Filmski in televizijski podnapisi v mnogo jezikih, na tisoče prevedenih podnapisov dnevno. Brezplačen prenos iz vira, podpora API, miljoni uporabnikov.</description>
		<description lang="sq_AL">Titra filmash dhe serialesh në shumë gjuhë, mijëra titra të përkthyera që vendosen çdo ditë. Shkarko nga burimi, apo nga mbështetja e API-së, miliona përdorues.</description>
		<description lang="sr_CS">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, hiljade prevoda okačenih svakodnevno. Besplatno skidanje sa izvora, podrška za API, milioni korisnika.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Filmer och Tv-undertexter med olika språk, tusentals översatta undertexter uppladdade dagligen. Gratis nerladdning från källor, API support, miljoner av användare.</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Her gün eklenen, pek çok dildeki binlerce film ve dizi altyazısı. Kaynağından ücretsiz indirme, API desteği ve milyonlarca kullanıcı.</description>
		<description lang="uz_UZ">Film va TV Taglavhalari ko'p tillarda, minglab tarjima qilingan taglavhalar har kuni tizimga yuklanadi. Bepul resursdan yuklab oling, API qo'llaydi, millionlab foydalanuvchilar.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">多语种的电影及剧集字幕，每日更新千余条翻译好的字幕。免费下载，提供API接口，已拥有上百万的用户。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Users need to provide OpenSubtitles.org username and password in add-on configuration</disclaimer>
		<news>
v5.1.2 (2020-03-21) by enen92
- Fixes for python3/matrix. Remove sys.path.append.
		</news>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
		<forum>https://forum.opensubtitles.org/viewtopic.php?f=8&amp;t=15847</forum>
		<website>http://www.opensubtitles.org</website>
		<email>admin [at] opensubtitles {dot} org</email>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/media/os_logo_512x512.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/media/os_fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_1.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_2.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_3.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<source>https://github.com/juokelis/service.subtitles.opensubtitles</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.Toronto-Channels" name="BCI Greek TV" version="2.8.1" provider-name="BCI Media Inc.">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.1.000"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.8.8"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="2.8.6"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>video audio image</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">BCI Greek TV addon</summary>
        <description lang="en">This addon offers live streaming content mainly in Greek language</description>
        <summary lang="el">Πρόσθετο BCI Greek TV</summary>
        <description lang="el">Το πρόσθετο αυτό παρέχει ζωντανό περιεχόμενο κυρίως εις την Ελληνική γλώσσα</description>
        <license>GNU General Public License, v3</license>
        <news>2.8.0 (10-02-2021)
- Added new streams (Food channel, cetn, health channel), updated others
- Removed rtmp urls and accompanying setting
- Disabled radio choice

2.7.0 (28-12-2020)
- Updated youtube api keys
- Bumped dependencies</news>
        <website>http://www.bcimedia.net/</website>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.smr_link_tester" version="1.1.5" name="SMR Link Tester" provider-name="gujal">
    <requires>
        <!-- <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/> -->
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl.xxx"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="0.0.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.0.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>SMR Link Tester Addon</summary>
        <description></description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.kodiadult" name="TVADDONS.CO Adult 18+ Add-on Repository" version="1.0.0" provider-name="tvaddons">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="TVADDONS.CO Adult 18+ Add-on Repository">
	<dir>
		<info compressed="false">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/zips/</datadir>
	</dir>

    <dir>
		<info compressed="false">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-adult-repo/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-adult-repo/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-adult-repo/raw/master/</datadir>
    </dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Unofficial Adult 18+ Kodi Addons from TVADDONS.CO</summary>
		<description>Unofficial Adult 18+ Kodi Addons from the TVADDONS.CO Add-on Repository. Please visit www.tvaddons.co for support!

Kodi is a registered trademark of the XBMC Foundation. We are not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.</description>
         <disclaimer>This Kodi addon contains age-restricted materials. By entering this Kodi addon, you swear under penalty of perjury that you are over the age of 18, and over the age of majority in the location from where you are accessing this Kodi addon.  If you are under the age of 18 years, or under the age of majority in the location from where you are accessing this Kodi addon, you do not have authorization or permission to use. TVADDONS.CO did not make all the add-ons in this repository and is not responsible for their content.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
                <forum>https://www.tvaddons.co/forums</forum>
                <website>https://www.tvaddons.co</website>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.peertube" name="PeerTube" version="1.1.0" provider-name="Cyrille B. + Thomas B.">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.addon.signals" version="0.0.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Add-on for PeerTube</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">PeerTube is a free, decentralized and federated alternative to other video platforms (like YouTube).</description>
     <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This add-on is not developed by PeerTube team.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Extension pour PeerTube</summary>
    <description lang="fr_FR">PeerTube est une alternative libre, décentralisée et fédérée aux autres plateformes vidéo (comme YouTube).</description>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Cette extension n'est pas développée par l'équipe de PeerTube.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
    <website>https://joinpeertube.org</website>
    <source>https://framagit.org/StCyr/plugin.video.peertube</source>
    <news>Version 1.1.0 (30th April 2021)

New features:
* Support live stream
* Translate the add-on into French (thank you @DavidHenryThoreau)
* Add the description of each video and each instance in the UI
* Display a notification when the service has started to let the user know the videos can be played (may be useful on slow devices). The notification can be disabled in the settings.
* Display a notification when the download of the video starts
* Add the total number of pages in the "Next page" item
* Rearrange the settings and make some names more explicit
* The video filter from the settings (local/all-local) is now also used when searching videos
    </news>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.alivegr.logos" name="AliveGR TV Logos" version="1.0.2" provider-name="Twilight0">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false" type="AliveGR" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">AliveGR's TV channels logos</summary>
		<description lang="en">Logos are provided separately to allow easier distribution</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.indigo" version="6.0.00" name="Indigo" provider-name="tvaddons">
	<requires>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" />
	</requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Indigo is your gateway to the world of unofficial Kodi addons!</summary>
        <description lang="en">Indigo is your gateway to the world of unofficial Kodi addons! Please visit www.tvaddons.co for support.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Kodi is a registered trademark of the XBMC Foundation. We are not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation. Furthermore, any software, addons, or products offered by us will receive no support in official Kodi channels, including the Kodi forums and various social networks.</disclaimer>
        <language>en</language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <forum>https://www.tvaddons.co/forums</forum>
        <website>https://www.tvaddons.co</website>
        <source>https://github.com/tvaddonsco/plugin.program.indigo</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.realizer" version="2020.01.24" name="Realizer" provider-name="aenema">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
		<import addon="script.module.metalibrary" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" />
		<import addon="script.module.feedparser" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description>Realdebrid Cloud Addon with a twist!
		This addon is inteded for use with content that you currently own! The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.
		</description>

		<summary lang="en">Real-Debrid Cloud Addon</summary>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<forum>-</forum>
		<website>http://real-debrid.com</website>
		<source>-</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>-</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.freelivetv.tva" name="Free Live TV" provider-name="mhancoc7" version="0.6.9">
    <requires>
        <import addon="script.module.m7lib" version="0.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Free Live TV</summary>
        <description>Please support the continued development of Free Live TV by becoming a Patron [COLOR
            lightskyblue]https://patreon.m7kodi.dev/[/COLOR]
        </description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>https://m7kodi.dev</website>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.archive_tool" name="archive_tool" provider-name="Zach Morris" version="2.0.2">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="vfs.libarchive"/>
    <import addon="vfs.rar" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Python class for working with file archives</summary>
    <description lang="en">archive_tool is a set of common tools to work with the Kodi libarchive virtual file system</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE V3</license>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.premiumizerx" version="2021.04.23" name="Premiumizer (py3)" provider-name="aenema">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" />


	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
	<extension point="kodi.context.item">
		<menu id="kodi.core.main">
			<menu>

				<label>[COLOR red]Premiumizer[/COLOR]</label>
				<item library="context/updatecache.py">
					<label>New Cloud Cache</label>
					<visible>System.HasAddon(plugin.video.premiumizerx)</visible>
				</item>
				<item library="context/updatelibrary.py">
					<label>Update Library</label>
					<visible>System.HasAddon(plugin.video.premiumizerx)</visible>
				</item>
				<item library="context/contextTools.py">
					<label>Settings</label>
					<visible>System.HasAddon(plugin.video.premiumizerx)</visible>
				</item>
			</menu>
		</menu>
	</extension>

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description>Premiumize Cloud Addon with a twist!
		This addon is inteded for use with content that you currently own! The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.
		</description>

		<summary lang="en">premiumizer Cloud Addon</summary>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<forum>-</forum>
		<website>http://premiumize.me</website>
		<source>-</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>-</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.bitchute" name="bitchute" version="2.2.0" provider-name="winsomehax">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.routing" version="0.2.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
        <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.9"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Viewing videos from BitChute.com</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Viewing videos from BitChute.com</description>
        <language>English</language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0</license>
        <forum>https://github.com/winsomehax/plugin.video.bitchute</forum>
        <website>https://github.com/winsomehax/plugin.video.bitchute</website>
        <email>winsomehax@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/winsomehax/plugin.video.bitchute</source>
        <news>https://github.com/winsomehax/plugin.video.bitchute</news>
        <disclaimer lang="en">It's yours. If you break it, you can keep the pieces!</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="slyguy.disney.plus" name="Disney+" provider-name="Slyguy" version="0.6.4">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.slyguy"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py" provides="video">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en">Disney+ is the exclusive home for your favorite movies and TV shows from Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars, and National Geographic.

Subscription required.</description>
    <description lang="it">Disney+ è la casa esclusiva per i tuoi film e programmi TV preferiti di Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars e National Geographic.

Abbonamento richiesto.</description>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news>Fix search</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.catchuptvandmore"
       name="Catch-up TV &amp; More channel logos and artwork"
       version="1.0.9"
       provider-name="SylvainCecchetto,wwark">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Channel logos and artwork used in Catch-up TV &amp; More</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Channel logos and artwork used in Catch-up TV &amp; More</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-2.0</license>
    <website>https://catch-up-tv-and-more.github.io/</website>
    <email>catch.up.tv.and.more at gmail dot com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/Catch-up-TV-and-More/resource.images.catchuptvandmore</source>
    <news>
[Version 1.0.8]
[Add] Equidia and BSmart channel logo
[Version 1.0.9]
[Add] 6play, MYTF1, NRJ Play, myCANAL and RTLplay logo
    </news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.reddit_navigator" name="Reddit Navigator" version="1.1.0" provider-name="Twilight0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.1.000"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="2.8.17"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pyxbmct" version="1.2.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.20"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.8.10"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video audio image executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Reddit Navigator addon</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο Reddit Navigator</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Reddit Navigator is an addon able to browse Reddit and play various forms of media and show text comments</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το πρόσθετο Reddit Navigator είναι μια μικροεφαρμογή πλοήγησης του Reddit που επιτρέπει την αναπαραγωγή διαφόρων ειδών πολυμέσων και προβολή σχολίων και νημάτων</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Kodi is a registered trademark of the XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
        <language>en</language>
        <license>GNU GPL, version 2</license>
        <source>https://github.com/Twilight0/plugin.program.reddit_navigator</source>
        <size>1711463</size>
        <news>1.1.0 ~ 03-04-2021
- Change caching method
- Utilize another method for indexing images
- Remove authorization methods except the one that you can enter user/pass and obtain tokens
- Tweaks on thumbnails and fanarts
- Remove capability for playing plexus streams

1.0.X ~ 05-01-2020 - 19-01-2021
- Initial Version, forked from Reddit Browser
- Replaced urlresolver with resolveurl
- Changed some default settings
- Several bug fixes
- Changed artwork
- Changed user agent string
- Changed app token
- Restored a window call function which didn't work on Leia
- Removed "depth" variable because it was supposed to be used on flat comments tree
- Fixed saved items menu
- Fixed user icon for my account menu
- Fixed some misbehaviour on search menus
- Fixed reddit videos playback
- Removed capability to install plexus
- Simplified actions on advanced authorization option
- Added a cancellation button and exception handling on wrong username/password
- Optionally notify user on token refresh, now defaults to off
- Optionally open the first time prompt (read me)
- Removed the authorization options except the login with user/pass
- Various other minor tweaks</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.animaltv" name="Animal TV" provider-name="mhancoc7" version="0.5.1">
    <requires>
        <import addon="script.module.m7lib" version="0.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Watch live streams of animals!</summary>
        <description>Please support the continued development of Animal TV by becoming a Patron [COLOR
            lightskyblue]https://patreon.m7kodi.dev/[/COLOR]
        </description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>https://m7kodi.dev</website>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.premiumizer" version="2020.01.24" name="Premiumizer" provider-name="aenema">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
		<import addon="script.module.metalibrary" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" />

	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
	<extension point="kodi.context.item">
		<menu id="kodi.core.main">
			<menu>

				<label>[COLOR red]Premiumizer[/COLOR]</label>
				<item library="context/updatecache.py">
					<label>New Cloud Cache</label>
					<visible>System.HasAddon(plugin.video.premiumizer)</visible>
				</item>
				<item library="context/updatelibrary.py">
					<label>Update Library</label>
					<visible>System.HasAddon(plugin.video.premiumizer)</visible>
				</item>
				<item library="context/contextTools.py">
					<label>Settings</label>
					<visible>System.HasAddon(plugin.video.premiumizer)</visible>
				</item>
			</menu>
		</menu>
	</extension>

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description>Premiumize Cloud Addon with a twist!
		This addon is inteded for use with content that you currently own! The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.
		</description>

		<summary lang="en">premiumizer Cloud Addon</summary>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<forum>-</forum>
		<website>http://premiumize.me</website>
		<source>-</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>-</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.realizerx" version="2021.04.24" name="Realizer (py3)" provider-name="aenema">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" />


	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />


	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description>Cloud Addon with a twist!
		This addon is inteded for use with content that you currently own! The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.
		</description>

		<summary lang="en">Realizer Cloud Addon</summary>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<forum>-</forum>
		<website></website>
		<source>-</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>-</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.catchuptvandmore" name="Catch-up TV &amp; More" version="0.2.34" provider-name="SylvainCecchetto,wwark">
  <requires>
    <!-- xbmc.python -->
    <import addon="script.module.codequick" version="0.9.13"/>
    <import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" version="18.225.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pytz" version="2014.2"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.3.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.11.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyqrcode" version="0.0.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.tzlocal" version="2.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.future" version="0.17.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.0.4"/>
    <import addon="resource.images.catchuptvandmore" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <!-- Set reuselanguageinvoker to false while developing the addon, making it only true for the production version -->
    <!-- See https://kodi.wiki/view/Addon.xml#.3Creuselanguageinvoker.3E -->
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Catch-Up TV &amp; More : Replay TV, Live TV et bien plus encore.</summary>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Catch-Up TV &amp; More regroupe dans un même plugin Kodi l'ensemble des vidéos des différents services et chaînes de Replay TV (rattrapage TV) ainsi que l'accès au direct. De plus, cette extension vous permet d'accéder rapidement aux vidéos et contenus proposés par certains sites internet.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Retours de bugs, propositions d'améliorations ou d'ajout de contenus sont les bienvenue ! GitHub ou e-mail.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Catch-Up TV &amp; More: It's all in the title.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Catch-Up TV &amp; More brings together in one Kodi add-on all the videos of the various services and channels of catch-up TV and live TV. Furthermore, this add-on allows you to quickly access the videos and content offered by certain websites.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Bug reports, suggestions for improvements or content additions are welcome! GitHub or e-mail.</disclaimer>
    <description lang="he_IL">ההרחבה מאפשרת לך להתעדכן בתוכן השידורים תוסף אחד של קודי מרכז את כל קטעי וידאו של שירותים שונים וערוצי תוכן משודר. בנוסף, תוספת זו מאפשרת לך לגשת במהירות לסרטונים ולתכנים המוצעים על ידי אתרים מסוימים.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="he_IL">דוחות שגיאה, הצעות לשיפור או תוספות תוכן יתקבלו בברכה! ל-GitHub או אימייל.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Catch-Up TV &amp; More: Replay tv, Live tv en meer.</summary>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Catch-Up TV &amp; More brengt replay en live tv van verschikkende diensten en kanalen samen in één Kodi add-on. Bovendien stelt deze add-on u instaat video's van bepaalde websites makkelijk te benaderen.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Bug meldingen, suggesties ter verbetering of additionele inhouden zijn welkom! Via GitHub of e-mail.</disclaimer>

    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=307107</forum>
    <website>https://catch-up-tv-and-more.github.io/</website>
    <email>catch.up.tv.and.more at gmail dot com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/Catch-up-TV-and-More/plugin.video.catchuptvandmore</source>
    <news>
[Version 0.2.34]
[NRJ Hits TV - BE] Remove Live TV (not available anymore)
[NRJ Hits TV - BE] Fix Catch-up TV
[TeleQuebec - CA] Readd Catch-up TV
[NOOVO - CA] Fix Catch-up TV
[BFMTV - FR] Use DailyMotion to play Live TV
[Languages] Update po files
[LuckyJack - FR] Remove Live TV
[ABWEB - BE] Fix Live TV (thanks chamchenko)
[RMC Decouverte - FR] Fix Live TV
[MA] Add some live TV for Morroco (M24, SNRT, Medi1 and Telemaroc) (thanks chamchenko)
[RobTV - BE] Add Catch-up TV (thanks michaelarnauts)
[Live TV] Add full support for multilingual channels (IPTV Manager + TV guide)
[Equidia - FR] Add more Lives (thanks chamchenko)
[TVA - CA] Fix Catch-UP TV
----
Visit WebSite - http://mpdb.tv/#home which host the french forum used by users of CU TV and More
    </news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.amazon-test"
       name="Amazon VOD"
       version="0.9.3+matrix.1"
       provider-name="Sandmann79, Varstahl">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.6.3+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.mechanicalsoup" version="0.12.0+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyxbmct" version="1.3.1+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.4.4+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.1.3.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
             library="default.py">
	<provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Amazon Prime Video Streaming</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Amazon Prime Instant Video</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Movies and Television Shows for Prime Members</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Filme und Serien für Amazon Prime Mitglieder</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Möglicherweise sind einge Teile dieses Addons in Ihrem Land illegal, Sie sollten dies unbedingt vor der Installation überprüfen.</disclaimer>
    <forum>http://www.kodinerds.net/index.php/Thread/44211-Release-Amazon-Prime-Instant-Video</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/Sandmann79/xbmc</source>
    <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
      <clearlogo>clearlogo.png</clearlogo>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.tubi.m7" name="Tubi" provider-name="mhancoc7" version="0.2.0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="script.module.m7lib" version="0.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Tubi</summary>
        <description>Please support the continued development of Tubi by becoming a Patron [COLOR
            lightskyblue]https://patreon.m7kodi.dev/[/COLOR]
        </description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>https://m7kodi.dev</website>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<!--suppress ALL -->
<addon id="plugin.video.premiumize" version="0.0.14" name="Premiumize Cloud (for Leia 18.9 and older)" provider-name="premiumize.me">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Browse your Premiumize.me cloud</summary>
        <description>This addon can be used to browse and stream any videos present in your Premiumize.me cloud</description>
		<disclaimer>This addon is deprecated and is no longer updated. This addon supports Kodi up to version Leia 18.9.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>https://www.premiumize.me</website>
		<forum>https://www.premiumize.me/help</forum>
		<news>v0.0.14 Rolled back recent changes which resulted in hiding some video types, fixed file transfer view</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="slyguy.curiositystream" name="CuriosityStream" provider-name="SlyGuy" version="0.1.4">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.slyguy"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py" provides="video">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en">Home of Award-Winning Documentaries.

Subscription required.</description>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news>Update subtitles</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="slyguy.nebula" name="Nebula" provider-name="SlyGuy" version="0.1.5">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.slyguy"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py" provides="video">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en">Nebula is smart, thoughtful videos from your favorite education-y creators</description>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news>Add subtitles</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.a4ksubtitles"
       name="a4kSubtitles"
       version="2.8.0"
       provider-name="Unknown">
    <requires>
      <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
      <import addon="vfs.libarchive" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="main.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="main_service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">a4kSubtitles - Multi-Source Subtitles Addon</summary>
        <description>
Multi-source subtitles addon optimized for Seren and a4kScrapers.
Supports: OpenSubtitles, BSPlayer, Podnadpisi.NET, Subscene, Addic7ed
        </description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <license>MIT License</license>
        <website>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</website>
        <source>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot>screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <news>
[v2.8.0]:
  * Support tvshows with more than 250 episodes for episode id lookup when tvshow imdb id is provided.

[v2.7.0]:
  * Support tvshow imdb id, along with season and episode passed from video file url.

[v2.6.0]:
  * Support imdb id (movie or episode) passed from video file url.

[v2.5.0]:
  * Add TLS adapter fallback

[v2.4.0]:
  * Fix some ssl issues

[v2.3.0]:
  * Add concurrency error handling

[v2.2.0]:
  * Fix KODI 19 Matrix support

[v2.1.0]:
  * Fix Persian search in Subscene

[v2.0.0]:
  * Use IMDb as main source for all meta.
  * Retry on 503 (Service Unavailable). OpenSubtitles and Subscene seems to return it occasionally.

[v1.8.0]:
  * Remove SubDb (Site is down)
  * Make lib vfs optional since there are fallbacks and it is used as last case scenario. Thus making the addon installable on platforms which are not supported by lib vfs.

[v1.7.2]:
  * Improve results sort based on title match

[v1.7.1]:
  * Drop python meta as it prevents installations on pre Kodi 19 versions

[v1.7.0]:
  * Update python meta to enable Kodi 19 installations

[v1.6.0]:
  * Add option to auto download first subtitle result silently

[v1.5.0]:
  * Auto open search dialog only on movie and tvshow videos

[v1.4.0]:
  * Add option to auto open the search dialog when the video does not have subtitles

[v1.3.0]:
  * Improve tvshow year scraping

[v1.2.0]:
  * Use internal ZipFile for extraction with a fallback to vfs.libarchive

[v1.1.0]:
  * Improve imdb id scraping

[v1.0.1]:
  * Add screenshots

[v1.0.0]:
  * Invalidate BSPlayer results cache when download links expire
  * Extraction fallback: zip -> gzip -> raw

[v0.0.30]:
  * Add service names in ad detection
  * Removed the option to disable cleaning of ads
  * Add remote fetching of addic7ed data

[v0.0.29]:
  * Fix Podnadpisi download of results missing filename meta
  * Fix last results cache not invalidated on language preferences change

[v0.0.28]:
  * Attempt scrape of imdb id when missing
  * Improve filename parsing
  * Fix SubDB lang code
  * Fix Podnadpisi not returning release name

[v0.0.27]:
  * Attempt to auto-fix a garbled cyrillic encoded subtitles
  * Fix more encoding issues
  * Ensure progress dialog close even if the addon crashes
  * Apply color to service name in results and bold tags
  * Show notification if imdb id is missing

[v0.0.26]:
  * Support for Addic7ed
  * Improve cache of the last results
  * Don't show progress when showing results from cache

[v0.0.25]:
  * Fix cancellation thread exit

[v0.0.24]:
  * Show progress dialog only for search

[v0.0.23]:
  * Add progress dialog
  * Support cancellation

[v0.0.22]:
  * Fix meta string conversion issue

[v0.0.21]:
  * TVShow year scrape from imdb when necessary

[v0.0.20]:
  * Improve Subscene tvshow matching
  * Extract first sub file from zips when none is matched
  * Fix Podnadpisi not working properly for tvshows
  * Fix non-ascii video file title issues
  * Add tvshow tests

[v0.0.19]:
  * Update settings
  * Fix language code suffix format in the subtitle file name
  * Support for Subscene

[v0.0.18]:
  * Support for Podnadpisi.NET
  * Support for SubDB

[v0.0.17]:
  * Reuse KODI's Python language invoker
    * Improves performance on low-end devices when switching subtitles for best match
  * Url decode subtitle names

[v0.0.16]:
  * Cache last result
  * OpenSubtitles always queries:
    * by imdb id and title
    * by video file hash
  * Improve results ordering:
    * preferred lang
    * lang
    * synced
    * name match
    * rating
    * hearing impaired
    * subtitle service
  * Fix url with numbers matching in ads detection

[v0.0.15]:
  * Remove ads by default
  * Support for BSPlayer
  * Additional option for OpenSubtitles to use file hash (Limits results to exact matches)

[v0.0.14]:
  * Fix API and normal usage at the same time

[v0.0.13]:
  * Exclude development files from release

[v0.0.12]:
  * Removal of ads (Experimental)
  * Fix extract issue when file contains unicode symbols

[v0.0.11]:
  * Changelog in KODI

[v0.0.10]:
  * Inserted language code in sub filename

[v0.0.9]:
  * Implemented (orginal, default, none, forced_only) as KODI language setting
  * Fixed minor bugs in API implementation
  * Added .idea folder to .gitignore

[v0.0.8]:
  * opensubtitles should make max 2 requests for separate languages
  * lint updates
  * add tests for download

[v0.0.7]:
  * API class rename

[v0.0.6]:
  * fix core requiring handle even with API usage

[v0.0.5]:
  * expose API for usage without KODI
  * add tests for search

[v0.0.4]:
  * distribution process:
    * KODI repository with updates based on github releases
    * addons.xml and addons.xml.crc auto generation via git hooks
    * release automation on merge to master via Github Actions

[v0.0.3]:
  * general settings for configuring requests timeout and results limit
  * additional ordering of the results depending on the similarity ratio of the video file name and the subtitle file name

[v0.0.2]:
  * improve archive extraction support
  * limit the results and add requests timeout
  * fix OpenSubtitles authentication
  * handle debug logging detection issues

[v0.0.1]:
  * initial working version (search and download subtitles)
  * OpenSubtitles support with optional authentication
  * results ordering with preferred language ordered first
        </news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.retrobiostool" name="Retro BIOS Tool" version="0.5">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
    <import addon="script.module.routing"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="retrobiostool.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <!-- <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker> -->
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Retro BIOS Tool</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Retro BIOS Tool will scan a folder of your choosing and copy the appropriate files for use in Kodi game addons</description>
    <license>GNU General Public License v3.0</license>
    <source>https://github.com/zach-morris/plugin.program.retrobiostool</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.jpg</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.subtitles.gr" name="Subtitles.gr" version="3.7.0" provider-name="Twilight0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.1.000"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="2.9.8" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="service.py">
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Subtitle service addon "subtitles.gr"</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Υπηρεσιακό πρόσθετο υποτίτλων "subtitles.gr"</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Search and download subtitles from various sites</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Εύρεση και λήψη υποτίτλων από διαφόρους ιστοτόπους</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This service is only for Greek subtitles. It is not published nor endorsed by any of the sites supported.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Υπηρεσία μόνο ελληνικών υποτίτλων. Δεν έχει δημοσιευθεί, ούτε εγκριθεί από οποιοδήποτε υποστηριζόμενο ιστότοπο.</disclaimer>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <website>http://www.subtitles.gr/</website>
        <source>https://github.com/Twilight0/service.subtitles.subtitles.gr/</source>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <news>[B]3.7.0[/B]
- Increase maximum possible timeout for search requests
- Add separate setting for subtitles.gr sub download timeout
- Utilize fuzzywuzzy to find synced subtitles (minimum match ratio 50, default 75, max 100)
- Replace futures module with tulip solution
- Various other tweaks

[B]3.6.2[/B]
- Bug fixes for subtitles save function on vipsubs

[B]3.6.1[/B]
- Broaden search results for vipsubs.gr
- Allow subtitle to be saved both locally and within the manual choice
- Ask before overwriting existing subs</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.imagotv" version="1.4.0" name="ImagoTV"
provider-name="Thomas B.">
<requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
  <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.6.2"/>
  <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0"/>
  <import addon="plugin.video.arteplussept" version="1.0.2"/>
  <import addon="plugin.video.dailymotion_com" version="2.4.1"/>
  <import addon="plugin.video.peertube" version="1.0.0"/>
  <import addon="plugin.video.vimeo" version="5.1.4"/>
  <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.7.0"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
  <provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <summary lang="fr">Extension vidéo de la plateforme ImagoTV</summary>
  <description lang="fr_FR">ImagoTV est la plateforme vidéo de la transition</description>
  <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Cette extension n'est pas développée par ImagoTV.</disclaimer>
  <summary lang="en">Video add-on for the Imago TV platform</summary>
  <description lang="en_GB">ImagoTV is the video service of the transition</description>
  <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This add-on is not developed by ImagoTV.</disclaimer>
  <language>fr</language>
  <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
  <website>https://imagotv.fr/</website>
  <source>https://framagit.org/imago/plugin.video.imagotv</source>
  <assets>
    <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    <fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>
  </assets>
  <news>v1.4.0 (05/04/2021)

Nouvelles fonctionnalités :
- Les vidéos hébergées sur PeerTube peuvent maintenant être lues

==== English version ====

New features:
- Support the videos hosted on PeerTube</news>
</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.xbmchub" name="TVADDONS.CO Add-on Repository" version="4.0.0" provider-name="tvaddons">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="TVADDONS.CO Add-on Repository">
	<dir>
		<info compressed="false">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/zips/</datadir>
	</dir>

    <dir minversion="18.0" maxversion="18.9.0">
		<info compressed="false">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-release-repo/raw/master/leia/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-release-repo/raw/master/leia/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-release-repo/raw/master/leia/</datadir>
    </dir>

    <dir minversion="19.0">
		<info compressed="false">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-release-repo/raw/master/matrix/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-release-repo/raw/master/matrix/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-release-repo/raw/master/matrix/</datadir>
    </dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Unofficial Kodi Addons from TVADDONS.CO</summary>
		<description>Unofficial Kodi Addons from the TVADDONS.CO Add-on Repository. Please visit www.tvaddons.co for support!

Kodi is a registered trademark of the XBMC Foundation. We are not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.</description>
         <disclaimer>TVADDONS.CO did not make all the add-ons in this repository and is not responsible for their content.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
                <forum>https://www.tvaddons.co/forums</forum>
                <website>https://www.tvaddons.co</website>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.git.browser" version="1.2.2" name="Git Browser" author="tvaddons">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
        <import addon="script.module.myconnpy" option="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Install Kodi Addons directly from GitHub</summary>
        <description lang="en">Git Browser for Kodi. Using this tool, you'll be able to install any Kodi addon that is developed or distributed through GitHub.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Kodi is a registered trademark of the XBMC Foundation. We are not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation. Furthermore, any software, addons, or products offered by us will receive no support in official Kodi channels, including the Kodi forums and various social networks.</disclaimer>
        <language>en</language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <forum>https://www.tvaddons.co/forums</forum>
        <website>https://www.tvaddons.co</website>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.iagl" name="Internet Archive Game Launcher" version="3.0.2">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.dateutil"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
    <import addon="script.module.routing"/>
    <import addon="script.module.archive_tool" version="2.0.2"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.8.7"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video game</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <!-- <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker> -->
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">The Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) is a FREE Kodi addon that will browse and launch games available from the Internet</description>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) es un complemento gratuito para Kodi que explora y lanza juegos disponibles en Internet</description>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="es_MX">Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) es un complemento gratuito para Kodi que explorará y lanzará juegos disponibles en Internet</description>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) é um addon gratuito para Kodi que explora e executa jogos disponíveis na Internet</description>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) é um addon gratuito para Kodi que explora e executa jogos disponíveis na Internet</description>
    <license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=231339</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/zach-morris/plugin.program.iagl</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen1.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen2.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen3.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen4.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen5.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen6.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.netflix" name="Netflix" version="1.15.1+matrix.1" provider-name="libdev + jojo + asciidisco + caphm + castagnait">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.addon.signals" version="0.0.6+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.5.0+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pycryptodome" version="3.4.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.myconnpy" version="8.0.18+matrix.1"/> <!--MySQL Connector/Python-->
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Plugin pro sledování filmů, seriálů online z Netflixu</description>
    <disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Použití tohoto doplňku nemusí být ve vaší zemi pobytu legální - před instalací dbejte na vaše zákony.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="de_DE">Addon für Netflix VOD-Dienste</description>
    <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Möglicherweise ist die Verwendung dieses Addons in Ihrem Land illegal, Sie sollten dies unbedingt vor der Installation überprüfen.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Netflix VOD Services Add-on</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">The use of this add-on may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Νέτφλιξ</summary>
    <description lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο υπηρεσιών κατά παραγγελία του Νέτφλιξ</description>
    <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Η χρήση αυτού του προσθέτου μπορεί να μην είναι νόμιμη στην χώρα που κατοικείτε - παρακαλώ ελέγξτε τους τοπικούς νόμους πριν την εγκατάσταση.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Bekijk Netflix films en tvprogramma's in Kodi.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Sommige delen van deze add-on zijn mogelijk onwettig in jouw land - raadpleeg de lokale wetgeving alvorens deze add-on te installeren.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="ja_JP">Netflix VOD サービスアドオン</description>
    <disclaimer lang="ja_JP">一部の国では、このアドオンを使用するのが不法でありますので、設置する前に必ず関連法律を確認してください</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="ko_KR">Netflix VOD 서비스애드온</description>
    <disclaimer lang="ko_KR">일부 국가에서는 이 애드온을 사용하는 것이 불법일 수도 있으니, 설치하기전 관련 법을 확인하기 바랍니다.</disclaimer>
    <description lang="it_IT">Netflix Add-on servizi VOD</description>
    <disclaimer lang="it_IT">L'utilizzo di questo add-on potrebbe non essere legale nel vostro paese di residenza - si prega di verificare le leggi in vigore prima dell'installazione.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">Complemento para los Servicios VOD de Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="es_ES">El uso de este complemento puede no ser legal en su país de residencia - Por favor, consulte las leyes locales antes de instalarlo.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Netflix VOD kiegészítő a Kodihoz</description>
    <disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Előfordulhat, hogy a kiegészítő használata nem törvényes az Ön országában - telepítés előtt tájékozódjon a helyi törvényekről</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Add-on para os serviços VOD do Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">O uso deste addon pode não ser legal no seu país de residência - por favor, verifique as suas leis locais antes de instalar.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Netflix VOD Hizmetleri Eklentisi</description>
    <disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Bu eklentinin bazı bölümleri ikamet ettiğiniz ülkede yasal olmayabilir - lütfen yüklemeden önce yerel yasalarınıza bakın.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Add-on pentru servicii video la cerere Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Utilizarea acestui add-on ar putea fi ilegală în țara în care locuiți - vă rugăm să verificați legile locale înainte de instalare.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Netflix VOD Service-tillägg</description>
    <disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Användandet av detta tillägg kanske inte är lagligt i ditt hemland - kontrollera med dina lokala lagar innan du installerar.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="zh_CN">Netflix VOD服务附加组件</description>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">此附加组件在您的居住国可能不合法-请在安装前与您当地的法律核对。</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Extension Netflix SVoD</description>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">L'utilisation de cette extension n'est peut-être pas légale dans votre pays de résidence - renseignez-vous avant de l'installer</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Wtyczka dla usług VOD serwisu Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Korzystanie z tego dodatku może być niezgodne z prawem w twoim kraju zamieszkania - przed zainstalowaniem zapoznaj się z lokalnymi przepisami.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="he_IL">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="he_IL">תוסף VOD לשירות של Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="he_IL">השימוש בתוסף זה עלול להיות לא חוקי במדינת מגוריך - אנא בדוק את החוק ברשות המקומית לפני ההתקנה</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="zh_TW">Netflix VOD服務套件</description>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_TW">在您居住的國家使用此套件可能並不合法 - 請在安裝前與您當地的法律核對</disclaimer>
	<assets>
      <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
    <language>en cs de es fr he hr hu it ja ko nl pl pt ro sv tr zh</language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://www.netflix.com</website>
    <email></email>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=329767</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/CastagnaIT/plugin.video.netflix</source>
    <news>
v1.15.1 (2021-04-21)
- Fixed regression to ESN/Widevine window
- Fixed wrong selection of audio track for impaired
- Add latest changes to IPC
- Minor changes
    </news>
  </extension>
</addon>

<!--suppress ALL -->
<addon id="plugin.video.premiumizemetv" version="0.0.3" name="Premiumize.me TV" provider-name="premiumize.me">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Browse your Premiumize.me cloud</summary>
        <description>This addon can be used to browse and stream any videos present in your Premiumize.me cloud</description>
		<disclaimer>This addon supports Kodi from version Matrix 19.0.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>https://www.premiumize.me</website>
		<news>v0.0.3 renamed addon, fixed add</news>
		<language>en</language>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="context.subtitles.gr" version="0.0.7" name="Subtitles.gr menu item" provider-name="Twilight0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.1.000"/>
        <import addon="service.subtitles.subtitles.gr"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
        <menu id="kodi.core.main">
            <menu>
                <label>30003</label>
                <item library="resources/lib/check_sub.py">
                    <label>30002</label>
                    <visible>!ListItem.IsFolder</visible>
                </item>
                <item library="resources/lib/options.py">
                    <label>30001</label>
                    <visible>!ListItem.IsFolder</visible>
                </item>
                <item library="resources/lib/clear_cache.py">
                    <label>30004</label>
                    <visible>!ListItem.IsFolder</visible>
                </item>
            </menu>
        </menu>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="en_gb">Subtitles.gr global context menu item</summary>
        <summary lang="el_gr">Ενιαίο στοιχείο για το κόντεξτ (εναλλακτικό) μενού του Kodi για το Subtitles.gr</summary>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <website>https://alivegr.net</website>
        <source>https://github.com/Twilight0/context.subtitles.gr</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.playlistLoader" name="Playlist Loader" version="1.4.8" provider-name="osgioia">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.xmltodict" version="0.11.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.dateutil" version="2.8.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Playlist Loader</summary>
    <summary lang="he">Playlist Loader</summary>
    <description lang="en">Playlist Loader</description>
    <description lang="he">Playlist Loader</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
	<news>
1.4.8
- EPG fix for list of channel names under the same id number
1.4.7
- fix for weird/double channel name
1.4.6
- fix for absent icon source
1.4.5
- cache reload period for EPG
1.4.4
- EPG plot update
1.4.3
- Added Russian language support and minor EPG tweacks
1.4.2
- Added support for xmltv EPG
1.4.1
- Added support for #EXTGRP group tag.
1.4.0
- Forked of Nux007
- Add Support for Youtube.

1.3.0
- Added default icons.
- Added transparency to existing icons for better themes integration.
- Added virtual directories feature allowing a better categorization of m3u lists.
- Refresh favourites list when moving an item.
- Ability to move playlists root and directories sides.
- Refresh playlists and directories when moving an item.
- Disabled TvDb and MovieDb for now ( waiting for improvements )

1.2.1
- Taking ownership of the addon, see : https://github.com/avigdork/xbmc-avigdork/pull/8#issuecomment-416955692
- Fixed regex => grouping issue when tvg-logo was empty.
- Added icon image also when items are grouped.
- Regex fix for title containing comas.
- Added TheTvDb scan for each lists in contextual menu ( beta ).

	</news>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.myaccounts" version="1.0.1" name="My Accounts" provider-name="Venom, Fen">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="lib/default.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="lib/service.py" start="startup" />
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" /> <!-- Must be placed after xbmc.python.pluginsource, otherwise the addon does not show in the repository. -->
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
		<summary lang="en">My Accounts Module</summary>
		<description>Single placeholder for all your accounts.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<forum></forum>
		<website>https://github.com/a4k-openproject/repository.myaccounts</website>
		<source>https://github.com/a4k-openproject/repository.myaccounts</source>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author is not responsible for the use of this addon. [CR]The author is in no way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.[CR]This is a Non-profit resource, organized solely for educational purposes which is protected under the Fair-Use doctrine of the Copyright Act, Specifically section 107, which does promote freedom of expression, by permitting the unlicensed use of copyright-protected works.</disclaimer>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot></screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>
[B][COLOR red]Initial Release - v1.0.1 – Sept. 21, 2020[/COLOR][/B]
[COLOR yellow]--[/COLOR][I] Kick off release.[/I]
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>
</addons>
